[
    {
    "option1": "We can go.",
    "option2": "We could goes.",
    "option3": "We could go.",
    "option4": "We could going.",
    "question": "আমরা যেতে পারতাম",
    "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Could we go ?",
    "option2": "Could we going ?",
    "option3": "Can we go ?",
    "option4": "Could we went ?",
    "question": "আমরা কি যেতে পারতাম ?",
    "correct": 1,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "We can not gone.",
    "option2": "We could not go.",
    "option3": "We can not go.",
    "option4": "We could not going.",
    "question": "আমরা যেতে পারলাম না",
    "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Perhaps we shall go.",
    "option2": "Perhaps we will go.",
    "option3": "Perhaps we will gone.",
    "option4": "Perhaps we  go.",
    "question": "আমরা বোধহয় যাবো",
    "correct": 1,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "We were thinking of going.",
    "option2": "We were thinking of go.",
    "option3": "We was thinking of going.",
    "option4": "We were think of going.",
    "question": "আমরা যাবো ভাবছিলাম",
    "correct": 1,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "We have to gone.",
    "option2": "We have gone.",
    "option3": "We have to go.",
    "option4": "We are going.",
    "question": "আমাদের যেতে হবে",
    "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Will we have to gone ?",
    "option2": "Shall we have to go ?",
    "option3": "Will we have to go ?",
    "option4": "Will we to go ?",
    "question": "আমাদের কি যেতে হবে ?",
    "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Can we not go ?",
    "option2": "Shall we not have to go ?",
    "option3": "Will we not go ?",
    "option4": "Shall we not gone ?",
    "question": "আমাদের কি যেতে হবে না ?",
    "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "We need to go.",
    "option2": "We are going.",
    "option3": "We shall to go.",
    "option4": "We will go.",
    "question": "আমাদের যাবার দরকার",
    "correct": 1,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Why are we going ?",
    "option2": "Why shall we go ?",
    "option3": "Should we go ?",
    "option4": "Why can we go ?",
    "question": "আমরা কেন যাবো ?",
    "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Why not we go ?",
    "option2": "Why can not we go ?",
    "option3": "Why shall  we not go ?",
    "option4": "Why not shall we go ?",
    "question": "কেন আমরা যাবো না ?",
    "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "When can we went ?",
    "option2": "When shall we go ?",
    "option3": "When is we go ?",
    "option4": "When shall we gone ?",
    "question": "আমরা কখন যাবো ?",
    "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Where can we go ?",
    "option2": "Where is we went ?",
    "option3": "Where is we to go ?",
    "option4": "Where shall we go ?",
    "question": "আমরা কোথায় যাবো ?",
    "correct": 4,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "With whom shall we go ?",
    "option2": "Whom to go ?",
    "option3": "Who to go ?",
    "option4": "Whom shall to go ?",
    "question": "আমরা কার সঙ্গে যাবো ?",
    "correct": 1,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "We want going.",
    "option2": "We want that to go.",
    "option3": "We want to go.",
    "option4": "We wanted go.",
    "question": "আমরা যেতে চাই",
    "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "We love went.",
    "option2": "We love will go.",
    "option3": "We have love going.",
    "option4": "We love to go.",
    "question": "আমাদের যেতে ভালো লাগে",
    "correct": 4,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "We have wish to going.",
    "option2": "We have to go wish.",
    "option3": "We wish to go.",
    "option4": "We wish going.",
    "question": "আমাদের যাবার ইচ্ছে  আছে",
    "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "If we could go.",
    "option2": "We have wished go.",
    "option3": "We wish that to go.",
    "option4": "We did wish to go.",
    "question": "আমরা যদি যেতে পারতাম",
    "correct": 1,
    "isPicture": false
    }
]